[
  {
    "front": "ouvrir, s'ouvrir",
    "back": "開"
  },
  {
    "front": "rentrer",
    "back": "帰"
  },
  {
    "front": "courir",
    "back": "疋"
  },
  {
    "front": "attendre",
    "back": "待"
  },
  {
    "front": "utiliser, employer",
    "back": "使"
  },
  {
    "front": "arriver, porter/mettre (vêtement)",
    "back": "着"
  },
  {
    "front": "servir",
    "back": "仕"
  },
  {
    "front": "faire, affaire, chose",
    "back": "事"
  },
  {
    "front": "chemin, route, voie",
    "back": "道"
  },
  {
    "front": "semaine",
    "back": "週"
  }
]
